Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Archive, 1983-1995
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Festival operations 1983-1993, IV.; Folders 443-511
  - Budgets and financial projections 1983-1993, A.; Folders 443-461
    Financial planning documents including budget drafts and notes, spreadsheet printouts, artist paylists, etc.
    Alphabetical by type of document
    - [Artist expense notes] 1984, 5 leaves (Box 9, Folder 443)
    - [Artist expense notes] 1986?, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 444)
    - [Artist expense notes] 1988, 5 leaves (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - [Artist expense notes] 1990, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 446)
    - [Budget memorandum, Bill Wachob to Jan Williams] 1983, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 447)
    - [Budget worksheet] 1986, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 448)
    - [Budget worksheet] 1988?, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 449)
    - [Budget worksheet] 1988, 10 leaves (Box 9, Folder 450)
    - [Budget worksheet] 1989, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 451)
    - [Budget worksheet] 1990, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 452)
    - [Budget worksheet] 1990, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 453)
    - [Budget worksheet] 1992, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 454)
    - [Budget worksheet], undated, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 455)
    - Final report: concert breakdown 1990?, 7 leaves (Box 9, Folder 456)
    - [Financial planning notes] 1984?, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 457)
    - [Paylist] 1984?, 15 leaves (Box 9, Folder 458)
    - [Paylist] 1985, 4 booklets (Box 9, Folder 459)
    - [Paylist] 1986, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 460)
    - [Paylist] 1988, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 461)
  - Concert planning and logistics 1983-1993, B.; Folders 462-477
    Program booklet drafts, rehearsal schedules and diagrams, working notes and do-lists, equipment orders, visa extensions, etc.
    - [Charts: program details] 1983, 15 leaves (Box 9, Folder 462)
    - [Draft copy: program booklet] 1986, 18 leaves (Box 9, Folder 463)
    - [Draft copy: program schedule] 1986, 8 leaves (Box 9, Folder 464)
    - [List: harpsichord works] 1987, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 465)
    - [Memorandum: equipment moving; from Jan Williams to M.O.C. University Movers] 1985, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 466)
    - [Memorandum: managing director tasks; from Bernadette Speach] 1984, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 467)
    - [Memorandum: performance details; from Judy to Yvar and Jan] 1985, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 468)
    - [Memorandum: piano moving; from Joyce Grant to Herman Movers] 1986, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 469)
    - [Memorandum: room reservation; from Joyce Grant to Judy Coon] 1986, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 470)
    - [Notes: artist lodging] 1983?, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 471)
    - [Notes: planning and production] 1983?, 15 leaves (Box 9, Folder 472)
    - [Notes: proposals for discussion] 1986?, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 473)
    - [Notes: rehearsal schedule] 1983, 6 leaves (Box 9, Folder 474)
    - [Notes: rehearsal schedule] 1984, 8 leaves (Box 9, Folder 475)
    - [Notes: scheduling] 1986, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 476)
    - United States. Immigration and Naturalization Service. [Approval of visa petitions] 1989, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 477)
  - Vendors and venues 1983-1993, C.; Folders 478-500
    Vendor correspondence or purchase records such as receipts, invoices, and responses to inquiries.
    Alphabetical by name.
    - Accu-Typesetting, Inc. [invoice] 1989, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 478)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery [correspondence] 1985-1986, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 479)
    - Allentown Industries [invoice] 1989, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 480)
    - American Music Center [invoice] 1987, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 481)
    - Buffalo and Erie County Public Library (N.Y.) [correspondence] 1985, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 482)
    - Buffalo and Erie County Public Library (N.Y.) [script for slide show on history of the Library] 1986, 14 leaves (Box 9, Folder 483)
    - Burchfield Art Center [correspondence] 1992, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 484)
    - Destinations Unlimited [invoice] 1990, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 485)
    - Fischer (Carl) Inc., New York [correspondence] 1983, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 486)
    - Freudenheim Art Gallery [correspondence] 1985-1986, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 487)
    - G. Schirmer, Inc. [invoice] 1985, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 488)
    - Hallwalls (Museum) [correspondence] 1986 and undated, 4 leaves (Box 9, Folder 489)
    - Hotel Lenox [correspondence] 1988-1992, 6 leaves (Box 9, Folder 490)
    - J. Rocco Photo-Graphics [invoice] 1990, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 491)
    - The Juicery [invoice] 1990, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 492)
    - The Lord Amherst Motor Hotel [correspondence] 1983 and 1985, 4 leaves (Box 9, Folder 493)
    - Margun Music, Inc. [correspondence] 1983, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 494)
    - Marquee at the Tralf [contract, incomplete] 1990, 7 leaves (Box 9, Folder 495)
    - Oxford University Press [correspondence] 1984, 4 leaves (Box 9, Folder 496)
    - Perrone, Ben [invoice] 1988, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 497)
    - Pfeifer Theatre [corresondence, diagram] 1987, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 498)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Office of Publications. [invoice] 1990, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 499)
    - Trafalmadore Cafe [invoice] 1988, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 500)
  - North American New Music Festival 1983-1993, D.; Folders 501-512
    Various forms, form-letter templates, and exemplars.
    Alphabetical by institutional name.
    - State of New York. Standard voucher, undated, 5 leaves (Box 9, Folder 501)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Letter of agreement, undated, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 502)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Lecturer payment authorization, undated, 4 leaves (Box 9, Folder 503)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept. NANMF form letter: confirmation 1985, 3 leaves (Box 9, Folder 504)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept. NANMF form letter: performer assignments, undated, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 505)
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept.] NANMF form letter: request for alien information 1991, 1 leaf (Box 9, Folder 506)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept. NANMF form letter: rehearsal scheduling 1985, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 507)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept. NANMF form letter: thank you 1985, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 508)
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept.] NANMF form letter: miscellaneous drafts 1987, 4 leaves (Box 9, Folder 509)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Office of International Education Services, Request for IAP-66, undated, 5 leaves (Box 9, Folder 510)
    - United States. Immigration and Naturalization Service. Petition to classify nonimmigrant as temporary worker or trainee, undated, 4 leaves (Box 9, Folder 511)
    - WNED (Radio station: Buffalo, N.Y.). Broadcast agreement and memo, undated, 2 leaves (Box 9, Folder 512)
- Miscellaneous 1983-1993, V.; Folders 513-535, Cartons 1-2
  Various documents and notes that do not fall easily into the above categories or which do not directly relate to the Festival, such as new-music concert programs, mailing lists, and two small cartons of obsolete computer disks.
  - American Guild of Organists [correspondence] 1992, 1 leaf (Box 10, Folder 513)
  - Canadian Music Centre. International year of Canadian music [prospectus] 1986, 9 leaves (Box 10, Folder 514)
  - Composers's forum network news, vol. 6, no. 4 Winter 1989, 8 pages (Box 10, Folder 515)
  - Deutsche Ensemble Akademie [newspaper]. Frankfurt am Main, Germany May 1990, 8 pages (Box 10, Folder 516)
  - Fundação Calouste Gulbenkian. 9os encontros Gulbenkian de música contemporânea [concert series brochure] 1985, 1 Folder (Box 10, Folder 517)
  - Greenwich House Auditorium. Essential music [concert program] 1989, 1 leaf (Box 10, Folder 518)
  - [List: addresses.] 1990?, 50 leaves (Box 10, Folder 519)
  - [List: addresses for NANMF participants outside the U.S.A.] 1989?, 11 leaves (Box 10, Folder 520)
  - [List: addresses of news-release recipients] 1991, 19 leaves (Box 10, Folder 521)
  - [List: composers/titles for tangos)] 1986?, 2 leaves (Box 10, Folder 522)
  - [List: telephone numbers of NANMF participants]) 1992, 4 leaves (Box 10, Folder 523)
  - Metalanguage. [Promotional flyer for recordings] 1984, 1 leaf (Box 10, Folder 524)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute. Perspectives on contemporary music [concert program] 1983, 1 leaf (Box 10, Folder 525)
  - Musical America [correspondence] 1985, 1 leaf (Box 10, Folder 526)
  - New Music America. [Music festival news release] 1983, 2 leaves (Box 10, Folder 527)
  - New York Philharmonic. Horizons '84 [concert series promotional brochure] 1984, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 528)
  - Score [computer program] reference manual [photocopy] 1987, Approximately 150 leaves (Box 10, Folder 529)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Campus map 1983?, 1 item (Box 10, Folder 530)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept. Compass [concert series promotional flyers] 1981-1982, 2 leaves (Box 10, Folder 531)
  - Symphony Space. The great American piano marathon [concert flyer] 1984, 1 leaf (Box 10, Folder 532)
  - United States. Immigration and Naturalization Service. Notice 1987, 1 leaf (Box 10, Folder 533)
  - [Miscellaneous news clippings] 1987-1991, 4 leaves (Box 10, Folder 534)
  - [Miscellaneous computer files] 1983-1991, 1 small carton containing 18 floppy diskettes (5-1/4 in.), including files written in the Appleworks program (Box 10, Carton 1)
  - [Miscellaneous computer files] 1983-1991, 1 small carton containing 19 floppy diskettes (5-1/4 in.) (Box 10, Carton 2)
- Photographs 1983-1993, VI.; Items 1-173
  Consists largely of artists' publicity photographs.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of principal subject.
  - 5th Species (woodwind quintet), undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 4 x 9 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-001)
  - 5th Species (woodwind quintet) at telephone booths, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 3.5 x 9.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-002)
  - Charles Ames, undated, 1 color photograph, 3 x 2 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-003)
  - Amherst Saxophone Quartet with instruments, in marble and wrought iron staircase, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-004)
  - Amherst Saxophone Quartet (Harry Fackelman, Michael Nascimben, Stephen Rosenthal, Salvatore Andolina) with instruments, on marble and wrought iron staircase., undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 6 x 9.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-005)
  - Larry Austin, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 6 x 4 inches; Beazley, Jerold (Box 11, Item NAP-006)
  - Milton Babbitt leaning on grand piano, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-007)
  - Milton Babbitt with Lejaren Hiller, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7.5 x 9.5 inches; Haupt, Irene (Box 11, Item NAP-008)
  - Milton Babbitt in computer room at Columbia-Princeton Electronic Music Center, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-009)
  - Martin Bartlett, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-010)
  - Eberhard Blum playing flute with Nils Vigeland on piano, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke (Box 11, Item NAP-011)
  - Eberhard Blum playing flute with Nils Vigeland on piano, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke (Box 11, Item NAP-012)
  - John Bergamo near trees with cymbal, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 3.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-013)
  - Charles Boone, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 6.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-014)
  - Lawrence Brose with Bolex camera, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Smith, Robert L (Box 11, Item NAP-015)
  - Earle Brown, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-016)
  - Buffalo New Music Ensemble with instruments (James Perrone, Marsha Hassett, Robert Schultz, Ferruccio Germani, Kunda Magenau, Paul Schlossman, Michael McCandless)., undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 6 inches; Bush, Diane (Box 11, Item NAP-017)
  - Buffalo New Music Ensemble, including Michael McCandless (piano), Donald Miller (trombone). Bernadette Speach (composer), William Ortiz (composer), Michael Colquhoun, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7.5inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-018)
  - John Cage, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Eder, Wolfram (Box 11, Item NAP-019)
  - John Cage, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Eder, Wolfram (Box 11, Item NAP-020)
  - John Cage, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Vater, Regina (Box 11, Item NAP-021)
  - Charles Casavant, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 4.5 x 3 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-022)
  - Joel Chadabe, electronics, with Jan Williams, percussion, in backgound, on stage at University of Illinois April 5, 1981, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-023)
  - Joel Chadabe with electronic devices, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-024)
  - Lawrence Cherney, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Ragsdale, Robert C (Box 11, Item NAP-025)
  - Chief Seattle portrait, undated, 1 sepia-toned photograph, 6 x 4.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-026)
  - Anthony De Mare with grand piano, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-027)
  - Robert Dick playing flute 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Sherman, Steve J (Box 11, Item NAP-028)
  - Robert Dick with flutes 1988, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Sherman, Steve J (Box 11, Item NAP-029)
  - Charles Dodge in electronic music studio, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-030)
  - Rinde Eckert, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Clement, Michele (Box 11, Item NAP-031)
  - James Emery with guitar, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Harris, Linda (Box 11, Item NAP-032)
  - James Emery playing guitar, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-033)
  - Michael Finnissy, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 6 inches; Ross, John (Box 11, Item NAP-034)
  - Morton Feldman, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-035)
  - Joan Fuzak, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-036)
  - Diamánda Galás, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Caravaglia, Tom (Box 11, Item NAP-037)
  - Isabelle Ganz, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Cravens, Patsy (Box 11, Item NAP-038)
  - Isabelle Ganz, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Arcidiacono, Patsy (Box 11, Item NAP-039)
  - Orlando Jacinto García, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Sperring, David (Box 11, Item NAP-040)
  - Jon Gillock with organ pipes in background, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 9 x 5 inches; Nicholson, George (Box 11, Item NAP-041)
  - Christian Wolff, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 4 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-042)
  - Kerry Grant, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Andrusz, Marlene (Box 11, Item NAP-043)
  - Granules (Musical Group), undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Crepo, Pierre (Box 11, Item NAP-044)
  - Granules (Musical Group), undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Crepo, Pierre (Box 11, Item NAP-045)
  - Lejaren Hiller, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5.5 x 4.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-046)
  - Julie Kabat at piano keyboard, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Kalischer, Clemens (Box 11, Item NAP-047)
  - Takehisa Kosugi with electronic equipment, undated, 1 color photograph, 6 x 4 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-048)
  - Al Kryszak on sofa, wearing sunglasses, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-049)
  - Joan La Barbara, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Freeman, Betty (Box 11, Item NAP-050)
  - Joan La Barbara: three pictures of Joan singing into a piano., undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 9 x 4.5inches; Richardson, Debbie (Box 11, Item NAP-051)
  - Joan La Barbara, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 6.5 x 8 inches; Woodman, Donald (Box 11, Item NAP-052)
  - Otto Laske, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 2 x 2 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-053)
  - Jesse Levine, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-054)
  - Jesse Levine, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-055)
  - Frieda and Stephen Manes seated at grand piano, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 9.5 x 7 inches; Schaaf, Peter (Box 11, Item NAP-056)
  - Freida and Sephen Manes standing at grand piano, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 9 x 7 inches; Schaaf, Peter (Box 11, Item NAP-057)
  - Bunita Marcus 1983, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Sloman, Steven (Box 11, Item NAP-058)
  - Michael McCandless, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 9 x 7inches; Bush, Diane (Box 11, Item NAP-059)
  - Michael McCandless, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 9 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-060)
  - Philip Mead at piano keyboard with Stepen Monahan writing music, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-061)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing at grand piano, 1979; 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Miles, Joann (Box 11, Item NAP-062)
  - Gordon Monahan, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Jones, Jeremy (Box 11, Item NAP-063)
  - Stephen Montague with score and poster, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Taylor, Angela (Box 11, Item NAP-064)
  - Carman Moore, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-065)
  - János Negyesy playing the violin, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 6 x 4 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-066)
  - New Winds musical group with instruments (Robert Dick, Ned Rothenberg, J.D.Parran), undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7.5 x 7.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-067)
  - New Winds (Robert Dick, J. D. Parran, and Ned Rothenberg) playing instruments, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 6.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-068)
  - New York New Music Ensemble members Linda Quan (violin), Jean Kopperud (clarinet), Chris Finckel (violoncello), James Winn (piano), Jayn Rosenfeld (flute), Daniel Druckman (percussion), undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 11, Item NAP-069)
  - Dora Ohrenstein 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-070)
  - Dora Ohrenstein 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-071)
  - Pauline Oliveros playing the accordion, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7.5 x 7.5 inches; Cohen, Becky (Box 12, Item NAP-072)
  - William Ortiz, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-073)
  - Carol Plantamura, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-074)
  - Michael Pugliese holding six yarn mallets, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 6.5 inches; Busacca, Larry (Box 12, Item NAP-075)
  - Morey Ritt, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 6 x 4 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-076)
  - Neil Rolnick, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 6.5 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-077)
  - Stuart Shepherd, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 2.5 x 2 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-078)
  - Connie Schulz, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7.5 x 9 inches; Haupt, Irene (Box 12, Item NAP-079)
  - Haydée Schvartz, undated, 1 color photograph, 3 x 3 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-080)
  - Elliott Schwartz reading score at piano, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-081)
  - Elliott Schwartz, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-082)
  - Francis Schwartz, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-083)
  - Netty Simons, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 11 x 8.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-084)
  - SONOR: From left, Edwin Harkins (trumpet), Carol Plantamura (vocalist), Bert Turetzky (double bass), Cecil Lytle (piano), undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-085)
  - SONOR: Thomas Nee is shown conducting six instrumentalists (Bert Turetzky, double bass; others unidentified), undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-086)
  - SONOR: John Silber (left), Thomas Nee (front), Carol Plantamura (right), and two unidentified musicians, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7.5 x 7.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-087)
  - SONOR: 13 musicians some with instruments, some holding cards with letters S-O-N-O-R, undated, 1 photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-088)
  - SONOR: 12 musicians some with instruments, some holding cards with letters S-O-N-O-R, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-089)
  - SONOR: 22 musicians outdoors, some holding instruments, undated, 1 color photograph, 3.5 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-090)
  - SONOR: 22 musicians outdoors, some holding instruments, undated, 1 color photograph, 3.5 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-091)
  - SONOR members Philip Larson and Carol Plantamura, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 3.5 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-092)
  - SONOR members Philip Larson and Carol Plantamura, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 3.5 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-093)
  - Sound Pressure, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-094)
  - Sound Pressure, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-095)
  - Sound Pressure, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 4.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-096)
  - Andrew Stiller, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 4.5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-097)
  - Sun Ra, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-098)
  - Talking Drums (Bill Ruyle, Kory Grossman, Michael Pugliese), undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 6.5 x 10 inches; Busacca, Larry (Box 12, Item NAP-099)
  - Aki Takahashi, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 3.5 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-100)
  - Richard Teitelbaum, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 2 x 2 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-101)
  - Mark Trayle, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Sumner, Patrick (Box 12, Item NAP-102)
  - Barry Truax sitting outside 1983, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Trotter, Larry (Box 12, Item NAP-103)
  - Barry Truax, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 3.5 x 5 inches; Krueger, Guenther (Box 12, Item NAP-104)
  - David Tudor with electronic equipment, undated, 1 color photograph, 4 x 6 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-105)
  - Bertram Turetzky playing double bass, undated, 1 color photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Melzer, Manfred (Box 12, Item NAP-106)
  - Bertram Turetzky playing double bass with two unidentified percussionists, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-107)